Guide to the Group Research, Inc. Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Horace Mann League (Box 167)
  - Hosmer, Craig (Rep.), R-CA (Box 167)
  - House of Prayer for All People (Box 167)
    [See also Shower of Blessing.]
  - Household Finance Foundation (Box 167)
  - Houser, Theodore V. (Box 167)
  - Houston Endowment, Inc. (Box 167)
  - Houston Tribune, The (Box 167)
  - Howard, John A. (Box 167)
  - Howard Payne College, Brownwood, TX (Box 167)
  - Hruska, Roman L. (Box 167)
  - Hubbard, Orville (Mayor), Dearborn, MI (Box 167)
  - Hudson, Charles B. (Box 167)
  - Hudson Institute (Box 167)
  - Hugel, Max (Box 167)
  - Hughes, Earl M. (Box 167)
  - Hughes, Howard (Box 167)
  - Hughes, J. Russell (Box 167)
  - Human Events Subscription material, Washington, DC, 1972- (Box 167)
    [See also Frank Hanighen, Edna Lonigan, and the Group Reseach directory under Human Events, under "Human Events" (the publication), and under Special Reports -- Human Events.]
  - Human Events "Congressional Record" and newspaper clippings, Washington, DC (Box 168)
  - Human Events Hanighen Memorial Fund, Washington, DC (Box 168)
  - Human Events Miscellaneous material, Washington, DC, 1971- (Box 168)
  - Human Events Miscellaneous material, Washington, DC (Box 168)
  - Human Events Miscellaneous printed material from "Human Events", Washington, DC (Box 168)
  - Human Events Miscellaneous issues of "Human Events", Washington, DC (Box 168)
  - Human Events Political Action Conference, Washington, DC, 1964 (Box 168)
  - Human Events Political Action Conferences, Washington, DC, 1963 (Box 169)
  - Human Events Political Action Conferences, Washington, DC, 1962 (Box 169)
  - Human Events Political Action Conferences, Washington, DC, 1961 (Box 169)
  - Human Events Subscription material, Washington, DC (Box 169)
  - Human Life Foundation, Inc., The (Box 169)
  - Humbard, Rex (Box 169)
  - Humes, Theodore L. (Box 170)
  - Humor (Box 170)
  - Humphrey, Gordon (Sen.), R-NH (Box 170)
  - Hungarian Freedom Fighters (Box 170)
  - Life Line Foundation, Inc. Hunt, H. L. (and family), Dallas, TX, 1971- (Box 170)
    [Oil billionaire Founder, Facts Forum and Life Line Foundation See also H. L. Hunt Foundation and Broadcasting as well as the Group Research directory under H. L. Hunt, under "Life Lines" (a radio program of Life Line Foundation), under "Life Line" (a publication of the Life Line Foundation), under Life Line Foundation, Inc., and under Special Reports -- Life Line Foundation, Inc..]
  - Hunt, H. L. (and family), Dallas, TX (Box 170)
  - Hunt, H. L. Columns -- Santa Ana Register, Dallas, TX (Box 170)
  - Hunt Foundation, H. L. Dallas, TX (Box 171)
    [See also H. L. Hunt (and family).]
  - Hunt, Nelson B. (Box 171)
  - Hunter, Edward, Arlington, VA (Box 171)
    [Writer and lecturer, associated with the Congressional committees on brainwashing and anti-communism, Young Americans for Freedom, and Manion Forum among others Former Chairman, Anti-Communist Liaison See also the Group Research directory under Edward Hunter.]
  - Huntley, Fred (Box 171)
  - Hurlbert Foundation, Helen Hart (Box 171)
  - Huss, Walter, Portland, OR (Box 171)
    [Former director, Freedom Center Founder-publisher, "National Eagle" See also "The Eagle" and the Group Research directory under Walter Huss.]
  - Hutcheson, Harold G. and Betty S. (Box 171)
  - E. F. Hutton and Company Hutton, Edward F. New York, NY (Box 171)
    [Associated with the American Liberty League and the Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge among others See the Group Research directory under Edward F. Hutton and under Special Reports -- Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge.]
  - Hyde Foundation, Arthur M. (Box 171)
  - Hyde, Douglas (Box 171)
  - Hyde, Henry (Rep.), R-IL (Box 171)
  - Ichord, Richard H. (Rep.), R-MO (Box 171)
  - "Ideas" (Box 171)
  - Ideas Unlimited (Box 171)
  - "Idler, The" (Box 171)
  - Igoe, Tom C. (Box 171)
  - Illinois Committee for the Constitution, Inc. (Box 171)
  - Illinois Congress of Conservatives (Box 171)
  - Illinois Small Business Men's Association (Box 171)
  - Immigration, 1987- (Box 171)
  - Immigration (Box 172)
  - I-M-P-A-C (Box 172)
  - Impact Publishers, Inc. (Box 172)
  - Impeachment (Box 172)
  - Improved Order of Redmen (Box 172)
  - "In a Nutshell" (Box 172)
  - Income Tax -- Drive to repeal, 1979- (Box 172)
    [See for extensive lists of federal tax cases and protest groups and their publications. Reported missing from box 08/2002]
  - Income Tax -- Drive to repeal, 1972- (Box 172)
    [Reported missing from box 08/2002]
  - Income Tax -- Drive to repeal (Box 173)
  - Independence Foundation, Inc. Portland, IN (Box 173)
    [See also DAWN and Council for Individual Freedom.]
  - Independence Foundation, Boston, MA (Box 173)
  - Independence Foundation, Philadelphia, PA (Box 173)
    [See also Donner Foundation, Inc.]
  - Independence Hall of Chicago (Box 173)
  - "Independent, The" (Box 173)
  - Independent Anti-Communist Committee (Box 173)
  - Independent Bar Association (Box 173)
  - Independent Citizens Council (Box 173)
  - Independent Electors (Box 173)
  - Independent Information Institute (Box 173)
  - Independent Research Associates, Inc. (Box 173)
  - Independent Research Service (Box 173)
  - Independent Teachers Association of California (Box 173)
  - Indiana Americans for Conservative Action (Box 173)
  - Indiana Citizens Committee for Research, Inc. (Box 173)
  - Indiana Economic Education Foundation, Inc. (Box 173)
  - Indianapolis Citizens Forum (Box 173)
  - Indignant White Citizens Council (Box 173)
  - "Individual Party, The" (Box 173)
  - "Industrial News Review" E. Hofer and Sons, Portland, OR (Box 173)
  - Industrial Press Service (Box 173)
  - Industrial Relations Council, Salt Lake City, UT (Box 173)
  - Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc. (Box 173)
  - Industrial Workers of the World (IWW) (Box 173)
  - Infomat (Box 173)
  - Inform National Reports (Box 173)
  - Information Council of the Americas (INCA) (Box 174)
  - Information Digest (Box 174)
  - Informers -- General (Box 174)
    [See also "Bugging," Police, Vigilantes, Wackenhut Corporation, Private Guards and Investigators, Military -- Civilian Spying, and Para-Military.]
  - Ingersoll Foundation, Rockford, IL (Box 174)
  - Ingram, T. Robert (Rev.), Houston, TX (Box 174)
    [Rector of St. Thomas' Episcopal Church and School and associated with Americans for Constitutional Action, the John Birch Society, Christian Freedom Foundation, Citizens' Councils, and Life Line among others See the Group Research directory under Rev. T. Robert Ingram.]
  - I.N.K.O. (Investigate Now King and Others) (Box 174)
  - Inner Peace Movement (Box 174)
  - Insider (Box 174)
  - "Insight and Outlook" (Box 174)
  - Institute for American Strategy, 1974- (Box 174)
  - Institute for American Strategy (Box 175)
  - Institute for Congress (Box 175)
  - Institute for Contemporary Studies (Box 175)
  - Institute for Defense Analyses (Box 175)
  - Institute for Economic Education, Inc. (Box 175)
  - Institute for Economic Inquiry, Chicago, IL (Box 175)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Institute for Economic Inquiry.]
  - Institute for Educational Affairs (Box 175)
  - Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis (Box 175)
  - Institute for Free Enterprise Education, The (Box 175)
  - Institute for Historical Review (Box 175)
  - Institute for Human Progess, Inc. (Box 176)
  - Institute for Humane Studies, 1982- (Box 176)
  - Institute for Humane Studies (Box 176)
  - Institute for Humanistic Studies (Box 176)
  - Institute for International Order (Box 176)
  - Institute for International Youth Affairs, Inc. (Box 176)
  - Institute for Labor Studies (Box 176)
  - Institute for Monetary Research, Inc. (Box 176)
  - Institute for Policy Studies (Box 176)
  - Institute for Propaganda Analysis, Inc. (Box 176)
  - Institute for Public Service (Box 176)
  - Institute for Research on the Economics of Taxation (Box 176)
  - Institute for Social Science Research, Washington, DC (Box 176)
    [See also American Enterprise Association and the Group Research directory under Institute for Social Science Research.]
  - Institute for Special Research, Pasadena, CA (Box 176)
    [Former Director, George Washington Robnett See also George Washington Robnett and the Group Research directory under Institute for Special Research.]
  - Institute for Studies in Federalism, Claremont Men's College, Claremont, CA (Box 176)
  - Institute for the Study of Economic Systems (Box 177)
  - Institute of American Relations (Box 177)
  - Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations (Box 177)
  - Institute of Cultural Affairs (Box 177)
  - Institute of Defense Analysis (Box 177)
  - Institute of Fiscal and Political Education (Box 177)
  - Institute of International Education, Inc. (Box 177)
  - Institute of International Labor Research (Box 177)
  - Institute of International Studies, University of South Carolina, Columbia, SC (Box 177)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations (Box 177)
  - Institute of Temporary Studies (Box 177)
  - Institute of World Policy (Box 177)
  - Institute on American Freedoms (Box 177)
  - Institute on Communism and Constitutional Democracy, Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN (Box 177)
  - Institute on Communism and Freedom (Box 177)
  - Institute on Comparative Political and Economic Systems, Georgetown University, Washington, DC (Box 177)
  - Institute on Religion and Democracy (Box 177)
  - Institute on Strategic Trade (Box 177)
  - Institute on United States Taxation of Foreign Income, Inc. (Box 177)
  - Insurance Companies and Executives (Box 177)
  - "Intelligence Digest" de Courey, Kenneth (Box 177)
  - Inter-American Association for Democracy and Freedom (Box 177)
  - Inter-American Education Foundation (Box 177)
  - Inter-American Foundation for the Arts (Box 177)
  - Inter-American Institute for International Political Research (Box 177)
  - Inter-American Press Association (Box 177)
  - Interchange Foundation (Box 177)
  - Interchange Society, The (Box 177)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Inc. -- Intercollegiate Society of Individualists "Academic Reviewer, The", Philadelphia, PA (national office) (Box 178)
    [Founder, Frank Chodorov See also Frank Chodorov and the Group Research directory under Intercollegiate Society of Individualists.]
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Inc. -- Intercollegiate Society of Individualists "Campus Report", Philadelphia, PA (national office) (Box 178)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Inc. -- Intercollegiate Society of Individualists Essay Series, Philadelphia, PA (national office) (Box 178)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Inc. -- Intercollegiate Society of Individualists Financial Information, Philadelphia, PA (national office) (Box 178)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Inc. -- Intercollegiate Society of Individualists General, Philadelphia, PA (national office) (Box 178)
    [See this file for several cross references.]
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Inc. -- Intercollegiate Society of Individualists "Individualist, The", Philadelphia, PA (national office) (Box 178)
    [Founder, Frank Chodorov See also W. H. Regnery, Frank Chodorov, and the Group Research directory under "The Individualist."]
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Inc. -- Intercollegiate Society of Individualists Other publications, Philadelphia, PA (national office) (Box 179)
  - Interdenominational and Christ Gospel Mission (Box 179)
  - Interdependence Council (Box 179)
  - Interfaith Foundation for Community Organization (Box 179)
  - Interim Committee for Independent Political Action (Box 179)
  - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 1972- (Box 179)
  - Internal Revenue Service (IRS) (Box 179)
  - Internal Security Act (Box 179)
  - International Academic Research Institute (Box 179)
  - International Advisory Council for Establishing a "Hall of Free Enterprise" (Box 179)
  - International Affairs Review (Box 179)
  - International Anti-Communist Brigade (Box 179)
  - International Anti-Communist Society (Box 179)
  - International Association for the Advancement of Ethnology and Eugenics, Ltd. New York, NY (Box 179)
    [See also "Mankind Quarterly" and the Group Research directory under International Association for the Advancement of Ethnology and Eugenics, Ltd.]
  - International Career Management Institute (Box 179)
  - International Catholic Truth Society (Box 179)
  - International Center for Economic Policy Studies (Box 179)
  - International Christian Leadership (Box 180)
  - International Committee for the Defense of Christian Culture (Box 180)
    [See also Foreign Intelligence Digest.]
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (Box 180)
  - International Conference Against Vivisection (Box 180)
  - International Council of Christian Churches (Box 180)
    [Former President, Carl McIntire See also Carl McIntntire and the Group Research directory under International Council of Christian Churches.]
  - International Development Conference (Box 180)
  - International Development Foundation, Inc. (Box 180)
  - International Economic Policy Association (Box 180)
  - International Evangelistic Association (Box 180)
  - International Executives Association (Box 180)
  - International Harvester Company (Box 180)
  - International Health Institute (Box 180)
  - International Institute (Box 180)
  - International Institute for Economic Research (Box 180)
  - International Institute for Strategic Studies (Box 180)
  - International Latex Corporation (Box 180)
  - International Marketing Institute (Box 180)
  - International Minerals and Chemical Corporation (Box 180)
  - International Movement for Atlantic Union (Box 180)
  - International Peasant Movement (Box 180)
  - International Platform Association (Box 180)
  - International Publishers (Box 180)
  - International Reform Federation (Box 180)
  - International Religious Liberty Association (Box 180)
  - International Rescue Committee (Box 180)
    [See also Vietnam.]
  - International Research and Studies Foundation, Inc. (Box 180)
  - International Research on Communist Techniques, Inc. (Box 181)
  - International Services of Information Foundation, Inc. "Inform", Baltimore, MD (Box 181)
    [See also the Group Research directory under "Inform" and under International Services of Information Foundation, Inc.]
  - International Social Service (Box 181)
  - International Society of Skilled Trades (Box 181)
  - International Students, Inc. (Box 181)
  - International Youth Federation for Freedom, Inc. (Box 181)
  - International Youth Federation for Freedom, Inc. (Box 181)
  - International Year of Youth (Box 181)
  - Internet (Box 181)
  - Interpol (Box 181)
  - Invest-in-America (Box 181)
  - Investment Bankers Association of America (Box 181)
  - Investors Diversified Services, Inc. (Box 181)
  - Investors in America, Inc. (Box 181)
  - Investors League and Union, Inc. (Box 181)
    [Formerly Investors' Union of America, Inc.]
  - Iowa Committee to Restore the Constitution (Box 181)
  - Irvine, Reed J. (Box 181)
  - Iszak, Frank (Box 182)
  - Italian-American Civil Rights League (Box 182)
  - Ithaca Reading Room Against Communism (Box 182)
  - Ivy Fund (Box 182)
  - Izzard, Wesley (Box 182)
    [Editor of "Amarillo News"]
  - J. I. Case Company (Box 182)
  - J. M. Foundation, The (Box 182)
  - Jackman, Theodore (Box 182)
  - Jackson, Donald L. Buffalo, NY (Box 182)
  - Jackson, Donald L. (Rep.), R-CA (Box 182)
  - Jackson, Henry M. (Sen.), D-WA (Box 182)
  - Jackson, Jesse L. (Box 182)
  - Jackson, Joseph H. (Rev.) (Box 182)
  - James, Daniel (Box 182)
  - James Madison Foundation (Box 182)
  - James, Tom (Box 182)
  - Jameson, Frank (Box 182)
  - Jarvis, Howard A. (Box 182)
  - Jefferson Educational Foundation, Washington, DC (Box 182)
  - Jefferson Educational Foundation, Columbus, OH (Box 182)
  - Jefferson-Lincoln Americans, Inc. (Box 182)
  - "Jeffersonian, The" (Box 182)
  - Jeffries, Jim (Rep.), R-KS (Box 182)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses (Box 182)
  - Jelke Foundation, Inc., Frazier (Box 182)
  - Jenkins, Woody (Box 182)
  - Jenner, William E. (Sen.), R-IN (Box 182)
  - Jennett, Richard P. Sherborn, MA (Box 182)
    [Author and columnist See also the Group Research directory under Richard P. Jennett and "That Man from Minnesota" (a book by Jennett).]
  - Jennings, L. A. (Box 182)
  - Jensen, Benton F. (Rep.), R-IA (Box 182)
  - Jepsen, Roger (Sen.), R-IA (Box 182)
  - Jesness, O. B. (Box 182)
  - Jewish Defense League (Box 183)
  - Jewish Right, The (Box 183)
  - Jewish Society of America (Box 183)
  - Jewish War Veterans of the United States of America (Box 183)
  - John Birch Society, Belmont, MA, 1986- (Box 183)
    [See also Series 2 -- John Birch Society and the Group Research directory under John Birch Society.]
  - John Birch Society General, 1976- (Box 183)
    [See also Series 2 -- John Birch Society.]
  - John Birch Society Newspaper clippings, 1976- (Box 184)
  - John Birch Society Newspaper clippings, 1960-1 (Box 184)
  - Johns, Lester P., Jr. (Box 184)
  - Johns-Manville Fund, Inc. (Box 184)
  - "John's Other Wife" (Box 184)
    [See also "The Thunderbolt."]
  - Johnson City Foundation (Box 184)
  - Johnson, D. Gale (Box 184)
  - Johnson, Frank J. (Box 184)
  - Johnson, Fred H. (Box 184)
  - Johnson, James E. "Johnnie" (Box 184)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. (Box 184)
  - Johnson, Manning (Box 184)
  - Johnson, Robert Wood (Gen.) (Box 184)
  - Johnson, Wallace E. (Box 184)
  - Johnston, Victor A. (Box 184)
  - Joint A.N.A.-A.A.A.A. Committee on Economic Education (Box 184)
  - Joint Committee Against Communism in New York (Box 184)
  - Joint Council on Economic Education (Box 184)
  - Joint Legislative Committee to Preserve the Peace, Alabama (Box 184)
  - Jones Foundation, Inc., W. Alton (Box 185)
  - Jones, Jenkin Lloyd (Box 185)
  - Jones, Linda (Box 185)
  - Jones, Mark Manderville, Princeton, NJ (Box 185)
    [Former president, National Economic Council. See also National Economic Council and the Group Research directory under Mark Manderville Jones.]
  - Jones University, Bob, Greenville, SC (Box 185)
  - Jordan, George Racey (Maj.), Los Angeles, CA (Box 185)
    [See also the Group Research directory under "From Major Jordan's Diaries" (a book by Jordan).]
  - Joseph Story Society (Box 185)
  - Judd, Walter (Rep.), R-MN (Box 185)
  - Judd Foundation, Walter H. (Box 185)
  - Junior Achievement, Inc. (Box 185)
    [See also Chamber of Commerce -- Miscellaneous publications.]
  - Kadets International (Box 185)
  - Kahn, Herman (Box 185)
  - Kahn, J. Kesner (Box 185)
  - Kalavitinos, George (Box 185)
  - Kamp, Joseph P. (Box 185)
  - Kane, Wanden M. (Box 186)
  - Kaplan, Jacob (Box 186)
  - Kaplan Fund, J. M. (Box 186)
  - Kasper, John (Box 186)
    [See also America's Future, Inc.]
  - Kassel, Dorothy (Miss) "Miss Kassel Says" (Box 186)
  - Katanga (Box 186)
    [See also American Committee for Aid to Katanga Freedom Fighters and Katanga Information Services. ]
  - Katanga Information Services (Box 186)
  - "Katanga -- The Untold Story" (Box 186)
    [See also International Affairs Review.]
  - Kaub, Verne P. (Box 186)
  - Kay, C. L. (Dr.) (Box 186)
    [Associated with the Lubbock Christian College See also the Group Research directory under Dr. C. L. Kay.]
  - Kazanjian Economics Foundation, Inc., Calvin K. (Box 186)
  - Keene, David (Box 186)
  - Keep America Committee (Box 186)
    [See also National Law Enforcement Committee.]
  - Keep America White Committee (Box 186)
  - Keisner, Ruth (Box 186)
  - Kelland, Clarence Budington (Box 186)
  - Kellar, Kenneth C. (Box 186)
  - Kellems, Vivien (Box 186)
  - Keller, Clinton G. (Box 186)
  - Keller, John (Box 186)
  - Keller, Werner (Box 186)
  - Kelley, William Donald (D.D.S.) (Box 186)
  - Kellog Foundation, W. K. (Box 186)
  - Kelly, George A. (Box 186)
  - Kemp, Jack (Rep.), R-NY, 1986- (Box 187)
  - Kemp, Jack (Rep.), R-NY (Box 187)
  - Kemper, James S. (Box 187)
  - Kemper Foundation, James S. Kemper Educational and Charitable Fund (Box 187)
  - Kendall, Willmoore (Box 187)
  - Kennametal Foundation (Box 187)
  - Kennecott Copper Company (Box 187)
  - Kennedy, Bill (Box 187)
  - Kennedy, Edward M. "Ted" (Sen.), D-MA (Box 187)
  - Kent, Tyler Gatewood (Box 187)
  - Kentucky Information Service (Box 187)
  - Keogh, Brooks (Box 187)
    [See also Series 3 -- North Dakota.]
  - Kephart, Calvin I. (Box 187)
  - Kephart, Robert D. (Box 188)
  - Kermit Roosevelt Fund (Box 188)
  - "Kernels" (Box 188)
  - Kerns, Bill (Box 188)
  - Kerns, William T. (Box 188)
  - Kerr, Walter (Box 188)
  - Kershner, Howard E. Christian Freedom Foundation, New York, NY (Box 188)
    [This file contains a list of cross references to publications. See also National Freedom Education Center and Christian Freedom Foundation as well as the Group Research directory under Howard Kershner and under "God, Gold and Government" (a book by Kershner).]
  - Kershner, Howard E. Columns, New York, NY (Box 188)
  - Kettering Foundation (Box 188)
  - Key Records (Box 188)
  - Keyes, Alan (Box 188)
  - "Keyes Report" (Box 188)
  - Keystone Advertising "Constitution News Review" (Box 188)
  - Khrushchev Visit Protest Committee (Box 188)
  - Kiamichi Missions (Box 188)
  - Kilpatrick, James Jackson (Box 188)
  - Kimberly-Clark Corporation (Box 188)
  - Kimmel, J. S., Sr. (Box 188)
  - King Associates (Box 189)
  - King Edward Cigars (Box 189)
    [See also Benjamin Franklin Historical Society.]
  - King, Gordon van B. (Box 189)
  - King, Martin Luther Assassination (Box 189)
  - King Ranch (Box 189)
  - King's College, Briarcliff Manor, NY (Box 189)
  - Kinsolving, Lester (Rev.) (Box 189)
  - Kinter, Arthur R. (Dr.) (Box 189)
  - Kintner, William R. (Col.) (Box 189)
  - Kirk, Claude Roy, Jr. (Gov.) (Box 189)
  - Kirk, Russell (Box 189)
  - Kirk, Russell Columns from "Santa Ana Register" (Box 189)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J. (Box 189)
  - Kirwan, John D. (Box 189)
  - Kissinger, Henry (Box 189)
  - Kissinger, Henry A. (Dr.) (Box 346)
  - Kitchel, Denison (Box 189)
  - Kiwanis Clubs (Box 189)
  - Klein, Julius (Maj. Gen.) (Box 190)
  - Kleindienst, Richard G. (Box 190)
  - Klinkert, Kenneth F. (Box 190)
  - Kluckhohn, Frank L. (Box 190)
    [Author, "The Inside on LBJ" and "Lyndon's Legacy" See also the Group Research directory under "The Inside on LBJ" and under "Lyndon's Legacy."]
  - Knight, Frances O. (Box 190)
  - Knight, Granville F. (Dr.), Santa Barbara, CA (Box 190)
    [Right-wing actitvist associated with the John Birch Society among others. See also the Group Research directory under Granville F. Knight.]
  - Knight, Robert L. (Box 190)
  - Knight, Vick (Box 190)
  - Knights of Columbus (Box 190)
  - Knights of Malta -- Sovereign Order of the Hospitallers of St. John of Jerusalem (Box 190)
  - Knights of Pythias (Box 190)
  - Knights of the Green Forest (Box 190)
  - Knights of the Kavaliers (Box 190)
  - Knott, Walter, Buena Park, CA (Box 190)
    [Founder, Knott's Berry Farm and California Free Enterprise Association See also Knott's Berry Farm and the Group Research directory under Walter Knott.]
  - Knott's Berry Farm, Buena Park, CA (Box 190)
    [See also Walter Knott.]
  - Know America Week (Box 190)
  - Know Your Enemies (Box 190)
  - Know Your Enemy (Box 190)
  - Koch, Fred C. Wichita, KS (Box 190)
    [Former president, Rock Island Oil and Refining Company and Koch Oil Corporation, Inc. See also the Group Research directory under Fred C. Koch.]
  - Kohler Family and Company (Box 190)
  - Korea (Box 190)
  - Korean Cultural and Freedom Foundation, Inc. (Box 190)
  - Kornfeeder, Joseph Z. (Box 190)
  - Kraemer, Fritz (Dr.) (Box 191)
  - Kramer, George N. (Dr.) (Box 191)
  - Kramer, Ken (Rep.), R-CO (Box 191)